<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book>
<note>
    <title> threats for disclosing the absurdly low PhD salary </title>
    <name>Romà Masana</name>
	<fullname>roma masana</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>PhD</programe>
	<field>Mathematics</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I was requested to meet the Director of the Graduate studies in Mathematics at IIT on December 23rd 2019. The director and the associate-chair of the 
	department in mathematics gathered me in a closed room and told me not to disclose my low salary to any other student, because other PhD students are paid
	even less and this was arising some conflict. They went on and directly threatened me of decreasing my pay if I talk to anyone else that PhD students in mathematics
	are only paid $16k per year. The other professor joined in and directly said that the disciplinary measures could extend themselves and that they wouldn't 
	write any recommendation letter for me in case I ever happened to apply for a posdoc after completing my PhD. They also said that 
	in case some employer called the math department to know about my performance, they would sadly have nothing good to say about me.</article>
  </note>
<note>
    <title> PhD students in Mathematics are getting paid late </title>
    <name>Romà Masana and 2 other students</name>
	<fullname>phd students</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st and 2nd</studyyr>
	<programe>PhD</programe>
	<field>Mathematics</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>For second time this academic year, our payments have been delayed by 1-3 months depending on the student. We recieve a small payment of $1600/month and we are left unemployed for 4 months every year, 
	and not happy with that the IIT even decides to pay us late for diverse reasons. This is unnacceptable for a so-called university of high standards. If you cannot even pay the lowest class workers on time, where does 
	all your reputation go?</article>
  </note>
<note>
    <title> IIT health and wellness center is no good </title>
    <name>Shivi M.</name>
	<fullname>shivi malhotra</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>masters</programe>
	<field>Data Science</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs>$1500/year for insurance </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>Do not rely on the IIT healthness and wellness center during emergency times. I had severe back ache today 
	(March 23rd and I had to rush to the medical center. Can you imagine that there was no doctor?!!!!!! I am pissed since this morning. </article>
  </note>
<note>
    <title> The teacher in tank </title>
    <name>The Clownfish</name>
	<fullname>Roma Domenech guillem alonso</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>PhD</programe>
	<field>Mathematics</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>Once upon a time, there was Professor in a tank.
Weeell, the HoLe was big, generous and plenty for ya’ll.
But the Professor felt alone.
He decided to make some friends, but since he couldn’t, 
And he had GoOD FinanCeS, he went to the Grad market to 
Buy some. There were many fishes in the stall. Carp, Cod and Clownfish were plenty in every 
shop. The brilliant instinct of the professor made him pick many Carp, a few Cod and two 
Clownfish. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;

In case you don’t know, Carps are very obedient, and will eat things that their master throw
 them that no other fish ever would. 
Cods, despite being whiter, are tasteless unless you
 spice them a bit. And even though the tank was just 55 Galloon, the luminous devices that
 were lying on the tank floor, made Cods think that they were in the Great Barrier Reef. 
&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Unlike the others, the Clownfish were depressed in the tank. Their flashy colors, and their
 mocking soul, were compressed between 6 walls. This is why they decided to make a HoLE. 
Every morning the Professor would ask to his fish, with a rhetorical tone, how life was. And all 
the fishes would bubble back. The Carps wouldn’t reply. The Cods would say “alles goed!!”
 And the Clownsfish would just smile: There is only one semester left until the tank flies apart.</article>
  </note>
<note>
    <title> Monetization of exams and homework is unjust </title>
    <name>Arika Ho</name>
	<fullname>william emily</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>masters</programe>
	<field>Data Science</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs>$127/semester </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>In my final exam I had to buy a $7 study pack for being able to do a question in the exam. Without it you cannot
	possible get an A  or a B on it. Will you pay for the pack? Of course you will, I paid $7 for it. We students 
	we have not choice. I think that having to pay for doing your own exams goes a bit too far. We already pay A LOT of money
	for our tuition fees, why do we have to pay extra money for doing our exams?? It makes no sense. Besides this in courses like MATH 151, MATH152 
	or MATH 251 (Calculus courses) you have to pay around $120 each semester if you want to have your homework graded. Shouldn't this be 
	already included in our expensive tuition fees? I wish the university would fund this or something..</article>
  </note>
  <note>
    <title> No room for rectifying our grades </title>
    <name>W.</name>
	<fullname>william emily</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>3rd</studyyr>
	<programe>undergrad Co-terminal</programe>
	<field>Chemistry</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I have no idea which grades I am getting during the semester. I can't possibly know my current average grade
	for each course and therefore I can't guess if I am working for a good grade or not until the semester finishes. Which
	leaves me with no time for rectifying my studying conduct. I would like to be reported in mid-semester of my overall grade 
	and how it compares to the rest of the class so that I can see if I need to work harder or not.</article>
  </note>
    <note>
    <title> We pay for doing homework?! </title>
    <name>W. and Greg</name>
	<fullname>william emily</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>3rd and 1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduates</programe>
	<field>Chemistry and Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $360/semester </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>We are quite frustrated that we have to pay for doing our homework. On top of paying our tuition fees we have to pay
	an extra $120 for creating an account of the webpage "Webassign". If we don't pay this amount of money, we cannot access
	Webassign and therefore we cannot check the new homework exercises, and what is worse, we cannot post our solutions to be
	graded. We think that submitting the homework should be a free action. We already pay around ~$40k of tuition per year, do we really have to 
	pay an extra $360 for being able to do our homework? Besies Webassign, the university requests us to open accounts on Zeplyn and "Flit it".
	Both of which cost $120.</article>
  </note>
   <note>
    <title>No funding for buying sports equipment </title>
    <name>Greg</name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $1000 </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I am member of the fencing Club. But we don't recieve enough funding for buying our fencing equipment. My fencing
	equipment costs $1000. The IIT funds $500, and I have to pay the other $500. What is fun is that then the IIT has 
	the right to keep all the fencing equipment and I can only get to use it as long as I fence on campus. I think that maybe
	the university should fund less sandwiches and more the fencing equipment. Specially if I pay half of the cost and I 
	don't have the right to own it.</article>
  </note>
  <note>
    <title>Misuse of activity fee? </title>
    <name>W.</name>
	<fullname>will emily</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>3rd</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Chemistry</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $125/semester </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I have witnessed some organizations buying around 400 sandwiches for a meeting of 20 people. I have the 
feeling that sometimes money coming from this fees is being wasted. "It's like a place of kids run by kids".	</article>
  </note>
     <note>
    <title>The contradictory life at MSV </title>
    <name>Greg and W.</name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st and 3rd</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace and Chemistry</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $1000/month </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>It's fun to know that the new residence hall (Bailey's) is going to be renovated and will have three people rooms
	that are actually going to be smaller than the MSV rooms. The IIT forces students to live on campus for 2 years because otherwise 
	no student would go and live here, and then the MSV would be unsustainable for the university. In other words, they 
	would loose too much money. I just live now on a nice apartment that costs $500/month. However an MSV shared room costs
	around $1000/month. It is also fun the fact that MSV has a kitchen but no one is allowed in there. G: I have made a few
	maintenance requests for fixing the carpet of my room. It keeps coming up but nobody really fixes it. I already made 3 maintenance
	requests last semester. A person keeps coming to my room, lifts the carpet, and puts it back where it was. After a day or two
	the carpet comes up again. It's frustrating, sometimes I would like to tell to the university: "Do something!".</article>
  </note>
       <note>
    <title>Funny driers at MSV </title>
    <name>Greg </name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs>  </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>Since October 2019 only 2 out of 6 driers work at MSV. The rest are broken and remain unfixed. We dry our clothes in 
	the unexisting sun.</article>
  </note>
         <note>
    <title>Some boring Prof's </title>
    <name>Greg </name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs>  </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>Some Professors don't seem very enthusiastic about their presentations. And they are sometimes boring.</article>
  </note>
          <note>
    <title>Satisfied with the meal plan</title>
    <name>Greg </name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $3,275.00 /semester </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I have the Hawk unlimited meal plan and I am satisfied by it. The pasta is usually greasy. But it's alright.</article>
  </note>
        <note>
    <title>I can't find a job on campus</title>
    <name>A. </name>
	<fullname>adika Ml girl</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>masters</programe>
	<field>Data Science</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs>  </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I applied to Handshake but nothing comes back. I can't get a job on campus and I need the money.</article>
  </note>
</book>
