<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book>
  <note>
    <title> No room for rectifying our grades </title>
    <name>W.</name>
	<fullname>william emily</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>3rd</studyyr>
	<programe>undergrad Co-terminal</programe>
	<field>Chemistry</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I have no idea which grades I am getting during the semester. I can't possibly know my current average grade
	for each course and therefore I can't guess if I am working for a good grade or not until the semester finishes. Which
	leaves me with no time for rectifying my studying conduct. I would like to be reported in mid-semester of my overall grade 
	and how it compares to the rest of the class so that I can see if I need to work harder or not.</article>
  </note>
    <note>
    <title> We pay for doing homework?! </title>
    <name>W. and Greg</name>
	<fullname>william emily</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>3rd and 1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduates</programe>
	<field>Chemistry and Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $360 </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>We are quite frustrated that we have to pay for doing our homework. On top of paying our tuition fees we have to pay
	an extra $120 for creating an account of the webpage "Webassign". If we don't pay this amount of money, we cannot access
	Webassign and therefore we cannot check the new homework exercises, and what is worse, we cannot post our solutions to be
	graded. We think that submitting the homework should be a free action. We already pay around ~$40k of tuition per year, do we really have to 
	pay an extra $360 for being able to do our homework? Besies Webassign, the university requests us to open accounts on Zeplyn and "Flit it".
	Both of which cost $120.</article>
  </note>
   <note>
    <title>No funding for buying sports equipment </title>
    <name>Greg</name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $1000 </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I am member of the fencing Club. But we don't recieve enough funding for buying our fencing equipment. My fencing
	equipment costs $1000. The IIT funds $500, and I have to pay the other $500. What is fun is that then the IIT has 
	the right to keep all the fencing equipment and I can only get to use it as long as I fence on campus. I think that maybe
	the university should fund less sandwiches and more the fencing equipment. Specially if I pay half of the cost and I 
	don't have the right to own it.</article>
  </note>
  <note>
    <title>Misuse of activity fee? </title>
    <name>W.</name>
	<fullname>will emily</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>3rd</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Chemistry</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $125 </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I have witnessed some organizations buying around 400 sandwiches for a meeting of 20 people. I have the 
feeling that sometimes money coming from this fees is being wasted. "It's like a place of kids run by kids".	</article>
  </note>
     <note>
    <title>The contradictory life at MSV </title>
    <name>Greg and W.</name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st and 3rd</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace and Chemistry</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $1000/month </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>It's fun to know that the new residence hall (Bailey's) is going to be renovated and will have three people rooms
	that are actually going to be smaller than the MSV rooms. The IIT forces students to live on campus for 2 years because otherwise 
	no student would go and live here, and then the MSV would be unsustainable for the university. In other words, they 
	would loose too much money. I just live now on a nice apartment that costs $500/month. However an MSV shared room costs
	around $1000/month. It is also fun the fact that MSV has a kitchen but no one is allowed in there. G: I have made a few
	maintenance requests for fixing the carpet of my room. It keeps coming up but nobody really fixes it. I already made 3 maintenance
	requests last semester. A person keeps coming to my room, lifts the carpet, and puts it back where it was. After a day or two
	the carpet comes up again. It's frustrating, sometimes I would like to tell to the university: "Do something!".</article>
  </note>
       <note>
    <title>Funny driers at MSV </title>
    <name>Greg </name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs>  </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>Since October 2019 only 2 out of 6 driers work at MSV. The rest are broken and remain unfixed. We dry our clothes in 
	the unexisting sun.</article>
  </note>
         <note>
    <title>Some boring Prof's </title>
    <name>Greg </name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs>  </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>Some Professors don't seem very enthusiastic about their presentations. And they are sometimes boring.</article>
  </note>
          <note>
    <title>Satisfied with the meal plan</title>
    <name>Greg </name>
	<fullname>greg frater</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>undergraduate</programe>
	<field>Aerospace</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs> $3,275.00 /semester </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I have the Hawk unlimited meal plan and I am satisfied by it. The pasta is usually greasy. But it's alright.</article>
  </note>
        <note>
    <title>I can't find a job on campus</title>
    <name>A. </name>
	<fullname>adika Ml girl</fullname>
	<anumber>unknown</anumber>
	<studyyr>1st</studyyr>
	<programe>masters</programe>
	<field>Data Science</field>
    <country>USA</country>
    <university>Illinois Institute of Technology</university>
    <costs>  </costs>
    <semester>Spring 2020</semester>
	<article>I applied to Handshake but nothing comes back. I can't get a job on campus and I need the money.</article>
  </note>
</book>
